<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kcron</id>
  <extends>org.kde.plasmashell</extends>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kcron</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKCronxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KCron</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KCron</name>
  <summary>Task Scheduler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Planificador de tasques</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Planificador de tasques</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Plánovač úloh</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Auftragsplaner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Χρονοπρογραμματιστής εργασιών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Task Scheduler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Planificador de tareas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Tegumihaldur</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ataza antolatzailea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Tehtävien ajastus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Planificateur de tâches</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Planificador de tarefas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Planificator de Cargas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Pianificatore di operazioni</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">작업 스케줄러</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Takenplanner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Oppgåveplanleggjar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Harmonogram zadań</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Escalonador de Tarefas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Agendador de Tarefas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Планировщик заданий</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Plánovač úloh</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Jobbschemaläggare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Планувальник завдань</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxTask Schedulerxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">任务调度器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">工作排程工具</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Task Scheduler is a graphical front end to the standard "cron" utility. With it, commands (or "tasks") can be run at specific times, on a certain day or date, or at specific intervals (time between execution). </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El planificador de tasques és un frontal gràfic per a la utilitat estàndard «cron». Amb ella, les ordres (o «tasques») es podran executar en moments específics, en un dia o data determinats, o en intervals específics (temps entre les execucions).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El planificador de tasques és un frontal gràfic per a la utilitat estàndard «cron». Amb ella, les ordres (o «tasques») es podran executar en moments específics, en un dia o data determinats, o en intervals específics (temps entre les execucions).</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Der Aufgabenplaner ist eine grafische Benutzeroberfläche zum Standarddienstprogramm „cron“. Damit können Befehle oder „Aufgaben“ an bestimmten Tagen oder Zeiten oder in bestimmten Abständen zwischen der Ausführung ausgeführt werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο χρονοπρογραμματιστής εργασιών είναι ένα περιβάλλον χρήσης για το τυπικό εργαλείο «cron». Με αυτόοι εντολές (ή «εργασίες») μπορούν να εκτελούνται σε καθορισμένο χρόνο, σε ορισμένη ημέρα ή ημερομηνία ή σε ορισμένα χρονικά διαστήματα (χρόνος ανάμεσα στις εκτελέσει).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Task Scheduler is a graphical front end to the standard "cron" utility. With it, commands (or "tasks") can be run at specific times, on a certain day or date, or at specific intervals (time between execution).</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El planificador de tareas es una interfaz gráfica para la utilidad estándar «cron». Mediante ella, puede ejecutar órdenes (o «tareas») a una hora determinada, en un día o a una hora determinada, o a intervalos específicos (tiempo entre ejecuciones).</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Tegumihaldur on programmi "cron" graafiline kasutajaliides. Selle abil saab käske (ehk "tegumeid") panna käima kindlal kellaajal, kindlal päeval või kuupäeval või kindla intervalliga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ataza antolatzailea "cron" estandarrerako bitarteko grafiko bat da. Berari esker, komandoak (edo "atazak") ordu zehatzetan exekutatu daitezke, egun edo data jakin batean, edo bitarte jakinetan (exekuzio arteko denbora).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Graafinen käyttöliittymä standardinmukaiseen ”cron”-työkaluun, jolla komennon (tai tehtävän) voi ajaa tiettyyn aikaan tai määräajoin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le planificateur de tâches est une interface graphique pour l'utilitaire standard « cron ». Grâce à lui, vous pouvez lancer des commandes (les « tâches ») à certains horaires spécifiques, à certaines dates ou jours de la semaine, ou à des intervalles spécifiques (entre deux exécutions).</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O planificador de tarefas é unha interface gráfica para a utilizade estándar «cron». Con el as ordes (ou «tarefas») poden executarse en horas concretas, en días ou datas concretas, ou en intervalos específicos (tempo entre execucións).</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il pianificatore di operazioni è un'interfaccia grafica al programma «cron». Con esso i comandi (o «processi») possono essere avviati ad orari specifici, in certi giorni o in certe date, oppure ad intervalli specifici (tempo tra le esecuzioni).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">작업 스케줄러는 "cron" 유틸리티의 그래픽 프론트엔드입니다. 명령(혹은 "작업")을 지정한 시간, 지정한 요일이나 날짜, 또는 지정한 시간 간격마다 실행시킬 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Takenplanner is een grafische front-end voor het standaard hulpmiddel "cron". Hiermee kunt u commando's (of "takens") laten uitvoeren op specifieke tijden, op een bepaalde dag of datum of op specifieke intervallen (tijd tussen uitvoeren).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Oppgåveplanleggjaren er eit grafisk grensesnitt til «cron»-verktøyet. Du kan bruka programmet til å køyra kommandoar («oppgåver») til faste klokkeslett, på faste vekedagar eller datoar, eller etter faste tidsintervall.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Harmonogram zadań jest graficzną nakładką na podstawowe narzędzie "cron". Dzięki niemu, polecenia (lub "zadania") można wykonywać o danym czasie, o danym dniu lub dacie, lub w danych odstępach czasowych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Escalonador de Tarefas é uma interface gráfica para o utilitário-padrão "cron". Com ele, os comandos (ou "tarefas") poderão ser executados em horas específicas, num dado dia ou data ou com intervalos específicos (períodos de tempo entre execuções).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Agendador de Tarefas é uma interface gráfica para o utilitário padrão "cron". Com ele, os comandos (ou "tarefas") poderão ser executados em horários específicos, em uma determinada data ou dia da semana, ou ainda em intervalos específicos (períodos de tempo entre execuções).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Планировщик задач — графическая оболочка к стандартной программе cron. Приложение Планировщик задач позволяет запланировать запуск программ (задач) указанное количество раз в указанное время и дату или через указанный интервал времени.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Plánovač úloh je grafický frontend pre štandardnú utilitu "cron". Príkazy alebo úlohy sa dajú spúšťať v určenom čase alebo v určenom dátume, prípadne v špecifických intervaloch (časom medzi spusteniami).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Jobbschemaläggare är ett grafiskt gränssnitt för det vanliga verktyget "cron". Med det kan kommandon (eller "aktiviteter") köras vid specifika tider, en viss dag eller ett visst datum, eller med specifika intervall (tid mellan körningar).</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Планувальник завдань є графічною оболонкою до стандартної програми «cron». За його допомогою можна віддавати команди (або виконувати «завдання») у певні моменти часу, у певні дні або дати або з певним інтервалом (часом між послідовними виконаннями).</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxTask Scheduler is a graphical front end to the standard "cron" utility. With it, commands (or "tasks") can be run at specific times, on a certain day or date, or at specific intervals (time between execution).xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">任务调度器是标准“cron”工具的图形化前端。利用它，您可以在特定时间，一周中的某天，特定日期，或者按照某个周期 (运行之间的间隔) 运行命令 (或者“任务”)。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">《工作排程工具》是標準 cron 工具程式的圖形前端。使用這工具，指令（或「工作」）可以執行指定次數、特定的日期，或特定的間隔（執行間隔時間）。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kcron</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kcontrol5%2Fkcron</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kcron/kcron.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">preferences-system-time</icon>
</component>
